<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roman Senninger</title>
    <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Roman Senninger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://romansenninger.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/blog/</guid>
      <description>June 2022 - Folkeafstemning om forsvarsforholdet Visualisering af meningsmålinger om forsvarsforbeholdet Interaktivt kort I - valgsteders stemmeprocent Interaktivt kort II - valgsteders resultater Replication Data Please visit my Harvard Dataverse profile for replication files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Journal Articles  Senninger, Roman and Daniel Bischof (forthcoming) Do Voters Want Domestic Politicians to Scrutinize the European Union?, Political Science Research and Methods, 1-9. Online First.
 Senninger, Roman, Daniel Bischof and Lawrence Ezrow (2022) How Transnational Party Alliances Influence National Parties&amp;rsquo; Policies, Political Science Research and Methods, Vol 10, Issue 3, 651-658.
 Senninger, Roman and Jens Blom-Hansen (2021) Meet the Critics: Analyzing the EU Commission’s Regulatory Scrutiny Board through Quantitative Text Analysis, Regulation &amp;amp; Governance, Vol 15, Issue 4, 1436-1453.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roman Senninger</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an Associate Professor of Political Science at Aarhus University. My research focuses on political elites and political institutions in domestic and European Union politics.
Methodologically, I have a strong interest in (quasi-) experiments, computational text analysis, and spatial and geographic data analysis.
Email: rsenninger@ps.au.dk
Twitter: @r_senninger</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Fall 2022 The Role of Space and Geography in Politics: Theory, Method, and Application Summer 2022 Summer School of the ECPR Standing Group on Political Parties Spring 2022 Policy Evaluation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Papers</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/workingpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/workingpapers/</guid>
      <description> What Makes Policy Complex? Revise &amp;amp; Resubmit at Political Science Research and Methods  What Makes Politicians Attend to Societal Problems? Evidence from a Field Experiment and Interviews with Party Candidates (w/ Henrik Seeberg) How Simple Messages Affect Voters&amp;rsquo; Knowledge and Their Perceptions of Politicians - Evidence From a Large-Scale Survey Experiment (w/ Daniel Bischof) Do Citizens Reward European Union Funding? Evidence from Three Local Studies </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>