<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roman Senninger</title>
    <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Roman Senninger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://romansenninger.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/blog/</guid>
      <description>Replication Data Please visit my Harvard Dataverse profile for replication files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Journal Articles Senninger, Roman, Martin Bækgaard and Henrik Seeberg (conditionally accepted) Unsuccessful candidates are more concerned about electoral fairness than election winners, Journal of Politics. [Preprint]
Senninger, Roman and Henrik Seeberg (forthcoming) Which Information Do Politicians Pay Attention To? Evidence from a Field Experiment and Interviews, British Journal of Political Science. [Preprint]
Senninger, Roman (2023) What Makes Policy Complex?, Political Science Research and Methods, Vol 11, Issue 4, 913-920. [Preprint]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roman Senninger</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an Associate Professor of Political Science at Aarhus University.
My research focuses on political elites and political institutions in Europe. I seek to understand how politicians select and use information for decision-making.
Methodologically, I have a strong interest in (quasi-) experiments and computational social science.
Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m holding a three-year Semper Ardens Accelerate Grant from the Carlsberg Foundation for the project &amp;lsquo;POLABROAD - How and Why Politicians Learn From Policies from Abroad&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Fall 2023 Advanced European Union Politics Spring 2023 Policy Evaluation Fall 2022 The Role of Space and Geography in Politics: Theory, Method, and Application Summer 2022 Summer School of the ECPR Standing Group on Political Parties Spring 2022 Policy Evaluation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Papers</title>
      <link>https://romansenninger.github.io/workingpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://romansenninger.github.io/workingpapers/</guid>
      <description>Simplifying Politics: The Impact of Linguistic Style on Citizens&amp;rsquo; Political Knowledge and Beliefs About Politicians (w/ Daniel Bischof, 2nd R&amp;amp;R at Journal of Politics) Does European Union Funding Reduce Eurosceptic Voting? </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
